{
  "category": "link",
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "List",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Dom bez pozwolenia projekt](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLQtjzZpgm5vcxXBwvtDN6Af56o8ubtxw-&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.474Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[David Bohm and Krishnamurti: Conversations](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL1n30s-LKus4oQ5fCd6MJ17waAMCsgumf&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Handmade Hero Complete](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLnuhp3Xd9PYTt6svyQPyRO_AAuMWGxPzU&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Live in Houston](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_nzFObZEJg_W6fejWbly0MScO2G7NbxWKI&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Live at the Beacon Theater](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_meNuRLh8Hf6KThcV12mqeZLbsYWHR-zaA&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Word: Live at Carnegie Hall](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_kVdYOTN_kN5PeBO8h21jN-u4EvnP_QILA&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Live at Madison Square Garden](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_nPqPvLkHTJ9IqIIQwuggb_ZKGX7RDYTcY&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Live at the Comedy Store](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_kBwWLWm7tzZjGc4JmqL9HLNdBGB92Kq98&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Hilarious](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_mF-SqQ_TabVAu2G667LlDPNj5mg5r6hy0&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Sincerely Louis CK](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_mSkOoLzJwQcAm2IDaV4MK63iN1rUEUvLQ&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Oh My God](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_l6uJGDhvPrrq7L7v3T6mt1CC_he3ds_hg&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Shameless](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_libfAZvf1WOlG-RH9owObXLCjl8-gB7ww&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Chewed Up](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_nwhEoVyv0TGXg4WPJKwcJ86WKcK3dlbyo&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Louis C.K. at the Dolby](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_mauqctx3ksO-hUs51sKtgReB6EFzdSBf0&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Fundamentals Friday](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLvOlSehNtuHtWlH0UOZNtOn-FlFCn1GYw&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Electronics Tutorial - DC Fundamentals](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLvOlSehNtuHtVLq2MDPIz82BWMIZcuwhK&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Electronics Tutorials - AC Theory Series](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLvOlSehNtuHvD6M_7WeN071OVsZFE0_q-&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[EEVacademy Digital Design Tutorial Series](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLvOlSehNtuHs2LwEdDwTp3n7mxb-MyBbo&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Charles Bukowski audiobooks](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL_vM3SSgTbAwMez9teGWUk5rux2XdMIEB&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Coding in Flow Focus Playlist](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrnPJCHvNZuD7UpyqwawOjrAEAqLOh1rw&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Build a 2D Platformer Game in Unity | Unity Beginner Tutorial](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrnPJCHvNZuCVTz6lvhR81nnaf1a-b67U&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[TOP 150 - Video Game Soundtracks](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLJCXrsW_esBlb1BYfeNhY4kJQuNYoDpF_&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[J. Krishnamurti-\"Wolność od znanego\"](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLg1Cpo4RYr0oiOMnLaFlzW4mU6dfSSGwE&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[UG Krishnamurti - The Courage to Stand Alone](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLT4PWp8IQuUWsTmX_3XKAGQOZ_wIHWo37&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Build Your First 3D Game in Unity | Unity Beginner Tutorial](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrnPJCHvNZuB5ATsJZLKX3AW4V9XaIV9b&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Shop Class: Critical Deck Connections](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLv8J8XldbK382ODtZnySxib9YyTiq4qnb&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLJGnfFmap7N9BTHNv4mIaqgyv-Co1K0Sy&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Unity Full Game Tutorials](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLI5KGtDrj4HVInyXdx5N2oYUAb9U7rJ4L&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[No BS TS](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBJYFrpEzdO2EapvU0GOJ09n&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Javascript Made Easy](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBJmAHWnJbVnXsl71hiHCrQh&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Become a Pro React Developer](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBJs6rKouX5U8-tWJgTLaeKv&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Get To Know Frameworks Fast](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBLkQ5r31mMzsEweAIbtgVoV&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Learn React and TypeScript](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBJ4CBroxVBJEpAXoz1g-naZ&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[TypeScript Engine](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLv8Ddw9K0JPiTHLMQw31Yh4qyTAcHRnJx&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Making a career out of Web Development](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLNqp92_EXZBKew_BEeQkb1DAiW9nCYAg4&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[U.G.Krishnamurti \"Odwaga bycia samemu\" -Audiobook](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLhXtRI5_o8IpJSJ8MnuXj8PtoTk6i4xge&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[U.G.Krishnamurti - \"Mistyka, Oświecenie\" - Audiobook.](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLhXtRI5_o8IrCThAITfUkETTxQdbt6C6x&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[ENGLISH J. Krishnamurti](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL1n30s-LKus5uOY2xbRjAx_wPHnKvy_aW&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[The Manipulated Man, by Esther Vilar](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLPwkFl_WzinXvpeOgfuLTPaHgPpCgq3Cm&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Master React JS by Building Real Projects](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL6QREj8te1P6wX9m5KnicnDVEucbOPsqR&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Haxe and HaxeFlixel Tutorials](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLlsuNLOyHwF47l0fGM2pcInLUr6o0S6t1&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Basic Electronics Tutorials & Projects](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLa7G9a0g8LGL_ApmTcVPv_Z_QVHYrRw6G&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Dynamical Systems (with Machine Learning)](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLMrJAkhIeNNR6DzT17-MM1GHLkuYVjhyt&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Jesus Christ Superstar: Live Arena Tour](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLAuH7O4YtgOZpSVIOklpqgFRlFbgbGlyD&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Leonard Susskind - All Stanford physics lectures in order](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL6i60qoDQhQGaGbbg-4aSwXJvxOqO6o5e&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Krishnamurti - Freedom From the Known](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLYT3Of_Fx4pI9cA17bkJGtCk4xCHo_vey&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Lecture Collection | Particle Physics: Basic Concepts](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLF363FFF951EC0673&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Coding Music 2023](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=OLAK5uy_kuxRG9WqjfjKskY-tesDUxR5brUCM6qmg&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Careers and Unemployment Survival Guides Series](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLXa2-LFNPwPhbkh7oo9sNppzKTJWzWK5E&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[The Tim Dillon Show](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL1rjjPR33Cl01i7196r2b5Ym4P8fkW1Mu&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Mix - Elektryczne Gitary](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1WlgS-gYMcs&list=RDEM59lOsbYK4_EgexUQk3jL3Q)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Suggestion Site App](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLLWMQd6PeGY0cZFMqx5ijmdaD87sJKCsU&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[U.G. Krishnamurti on Freedom](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLPRw5Rb66-5MW7W1HpaRSCD45ZFH5sBU1&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Królowie Żyta](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLaXkCSvwkRCMCVjiPQ7X0GiWCJW4VpLGO&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "",
          "dateTime": "2024-06-09T17:31:50.917Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[How To Frame A Pier and Beam Cabin](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PL_RMlIP4db1WhgOD9W6NAUguft9Gvcz-t&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Start Here](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLLWMQd6PeGY2_L2WC6_VYVEoAb4KhDPDW&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Full Bible](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jx_65lT1pUc&list=PLs0kYUO87ryQ58A2PZGnrHd4Ie1zFPzbn)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:11:06.475Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Interesting",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Math for Game Devs [2022]",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[Math for Game Devs [2022]](https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLImQaTpSAdsArRFFj8bIfqMk2X7Vlf3XF&feature=shared)",
          "dateTime": "2024-06-09T17:34:14.908Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}